I spring fans welcome to another
我春天的歌迷欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips today we're
今天我们将介绍春季技巧
gonna talk about Redis Redis has become
谈论Redis Redis已经成为
an adequate as sort of general purpose
足够作为一般用途
appliance that everybody is and
每个人都是的电器
installed or used at some point and it's
在某个时候安装或使用的
made more readily available not least of
更容易获得
which because it's simple to use simple
因为使用起来很简单
to operationalize and simple to install
易于操作且易于安装
but because it well first of all it goes
但是因为一切顺利
out of its way to be accessible there's
使其无法访问
even support for example that someone
甚至支持某人
might use it using the memcache D
可以使用memcache D使用它
protocol and the company behind it Redis
协议及其背后的公司Redis
Labs has done a great job of making it
实验室在做到这一点方面做得很出色
as easy to consume as possible and a
尽可能容易食用，
number of different target platforms so
不同目标平台的数量
you can actually use Redis for example
您实际上可以使用Redis为例
in cloud memory right they have they've
在云内存中，他们拥有
provided the support for that using
为使用提供了支持
pivotal cloud foundry or pivotal web
关键的云铸造厂或关键的网络
services are hosted multi-tenant cloud
服务托管多租户云
platform Redis labs also goes I think a
平台Redis实验室也去了，我认为
step beyond they provide a number of
超越他们提供的一些
features that make Redis really
使Redis真正有用的功能
palatable for it so for example stock
适口，例如股票
Redis out of the box the open source
Redis开箱即用的开源
Redis has a strong correspondence
Redis具有很强的对应性
there's one server one database now so I
现在有一台服务器一个数据库，所以我
have multiple databases then it becomes
有多个数据库，那么它变成
a little TD so you have to run multiple
一点TD，所以您必须运行多个
servers they have a product that allows
服务器，他们有一个产品，允许
you to then manage all that right Dave
然后您可以管理所有正确的Dave
Nielsen over at Redis labs he likes to
Nielsen在他喜欢的Redis实验室工作
joke that it is a hard DBMS right a
开玩笑说这是很难的DBMS，对吧
Redis database management system in the
Redis数据库管理系统
same way that my sequel Oracle or post
与我的续集Oracle或发布方式相同
cards are our DBMS is but in their case
卡是我们的DBMS，但就其而言
of course they're talking about
当然，他们在谈论
relational database management systems
关系数据库管理系统
now Redis is most commonly known I think
现在我认为Redis是最普遍的
for for its use as a key value store but
用作键值存储，但
that I think dismisses or ignores the
我认为驳回或忽略了
the large swath of features in
大量的功能
functionality that that Redis provides
Redis提供的功能
there's a lot of use cases that are well
有很多很好的用例
supported by Redis that I think most of
我认为Redis支持大多数
us just take for granted or don't even
我们只是理所当然，甚至不
know they are there until we ignore so
知道他们在那里，直到我们忽略了
the goal here in this installment is to
本期的目的是
look at just this huge just just Swiss
看看这巨大的只是瑞士的
this amazing veritable Swiss Army knife
这把名副其实的瑞士军刀
of functionality that is Redis and to
Redis的功能
see how to build an app with it and see
了解如何使用它来构建应用程序并查看
how different aspects of the spring
春天的不同方面
ecosystem make using it and working with
生态系统使其使用并与之合作
it very simple so we're gonna build a
非常简单，所以我们要建立一个
new application here starting at start
从这里开始新的应用程序
to spring the veil and we're gonna take
揭开面纱，我们将采取
a manager of the auto configuration for
自动配置的管理员
spring spring boot and Redis
春天的春天引导和Redis
building application here called gonna
在这里建立应用程序
call this Redis so I don't see Redis
叫这个Redis，所以我看不到Redis
like so and we use the data Redis
像这样，我们使用数据Redis
support okay
支持好
now you notice that there is actually a
现在您注意到实际上有一个
reactive variant we could have used that
反应性变量我们可以使用
as well but I'm gonna use just regular
以及，但我将只使用常规
Redis will use Lombok we're gonna use
Redis将使用我们将使用的Lombok
the session support we're gonna use the
会话支持，我们将使用
cache abstraction support
缓存抽象支持
we'll use the web support alright so
我们将使用网络支持
we've got a number of different bits
我们有很多不同的地方
here that we want in our application in
在这里我们要在我们的应用程序中
order to be able to to be able to build
为了能够建立
this application we're gonna build a web
这个应用程序，我们将建立一个网站
app so I'm going to use time leaf as
应用程序，所以我将使用时间叶作为
well so just a lot of different
好吧，只是很多不同
functionality here that we can use you
我们可以使用您的功能
know to build a very simple application
知道构建一个非常简单的应用程序
but we're gonna hit a lot of different
但我们会遇到很多不同
points very quickly not focusing at any
很快就一点都不专注
one particular thing this is meant to be
这是一件特别的事
a smorgasbord of Redis if you're welcome
不客气的Redis的杂货店
okay so I'm gonna build a application
好吧，我要构建一个应用程序
here ueo reddit zip open this up in my
在这里ueo reddit zip在我的文件夹中打开它
IDE and we're gonna then we're gonna
IDE，然后我们要
then move in straight into the coast
然后直接进入海岸
right so I'm gonna build an application
对，所以我要构建一个应用程序
in order to be able to deploy this into
为了能够将其部署到
as we well later into cloud funder we
后来我们进入云资金商，
need to add the commons pool dependency
需要添加公共池依赖项
so I must remember to do that here
所以我必须记得在这里做
waiting for all the bits to download all
等待所有位下载全部
right palm that XML okay so Commons pool
右手掌，XML没问题，所以公共池
too okay and there we are there's our
太好了，我们在那里
new server radius application and we're
新的服务器半径应用程序，我们
gonna build to some application so we'll
将构建到某些应用程序，所以我们将
start with what I think most of us are
从我认为我们大多数人开始
familiar with which is the Redis
熟悉哪个是Redis
template now spring boot auto configures
模板现在Spring Boot自动配置
a couple of Redis converts here so let's
几个Redis在这里转换，让我们
look at the witness auto configuration
看见证人自动配置
here and we see that we are we have two
在这里，我们看到我们是两个
configurations for two different Redis
两个不同Redis的配置
client-side libraries now the other
客户端库现在另一个
thing you may appreciate is that Redis
您可能会欣赏的是Redis
itself the spring data rate is supports
本身就是弹簧数据速率的支撑
look at the Redis template is very old
看Redis模板很旧
this is one of the one of the first
这是第一个
modules that we added to spring data
我们添加到spring数据的模块
after neo4j
neo4j之后
and since the very beginning I think
从一开始我就认为
this has been here for almost got to be
这几乎已经到了
eight years now right at 2011 2010 so a
八年后的2011年，所以
long time that we've had this support in
很长时间以来，我们一直在提供这种支持
spring data it's one of the original
春天的数据，这是原始的之一
modules and so it's gone through a lot
模块，所以它经历了很多
of evolutions but fundamentally at the
进化论，但从根本上讲
core there's always been a few core
核心总是有一些核心
concepts including this rightist
包括这个右派在内的概念
template this rightist template very
这个右派模板
much like other templates in the Spring
与春季的其他模板非常相似
Framework eco system is a thing that
框架生态系统是
handles tedious resource initialization
处理乏味的资源初始化
and acquisition and acquisition and
以及收购和收购以及
let's just focus on the business logic
让我们只关注业务逻辑
that we want to express so things like
我们想要表达的东西
issuing queries and doing updates and
发出查询并进行更新，以及
and so on are easy to do they become
等等很容易做到
one-liners usually and the things that
单线通常以及
we don't want to waste time on like you
我们不想像你一样浪费时间
know setting up a connection and setting
知道建立连接和设置
up a session and all that stuff and
进行会议以及所有这些东西
managing all the result sets and all
管理所有结果集和所有
that stuff just be able to iterate over
这些东西只是能够迭代
them all that stuff is managed for us by
他们所有的东西都由我们来管理
this template this template is keyed
此模板此模板已锁定
it's genericized in terms of the key
它在密钥方面是通用的
type that we're going to use so remember
我们将要使用的类型，请记住
Redis is fundamentally a key value store
从根本上说，Redis是关键值存储
but the values themselves can be all
但价值观本身可以是全部
sorts of different things you can have
您可以拥有的各种不同的东西
other dictionaries or Maps right or they
其他词典或地图权利，或者他们
call it a hash as values you can have a
将其称为哈希值，您可以拥有一个
cue right so you can simulate pub/sub
提示正确，因此您可以模拟发布/订阅
with redness you can do you can have geo
发红，你可以做，你可以有地理
spatial indexes as values you can do
空间索引作为您可以做的值
atomic numbers and semaphores these
原子序号和信号量
kinds of things as values so there's a
作为价值的东西，所以有一个
lot of really sophisticated values that
许多非常复杂的价值观
you can put there but ultimately they
你可以放在那里，但最终他们
have a key and of course your values
有一把钥匙，当然还有你的价值观
could just be arbitrary you know blobs
可能是任意的，您知道斑点
of data and and that is the first thing
数据，这是第一件事
that we have to understand here is that
我们在这里必须了解的是
Redis doesn't care how we encode our
Redis不在乎我们如何编码我们的
data that data can live in Redis as just
数据可以只存在于Redis中
a series of bytes for example it can
例如一系列字节
live as JSON you know you know whatever
像JSON一样生活，您知道
you want it's up to you as a client you
您希望由客户决定
of that database to specify that when
该数据库以指定何时
you create the template now here as a
您现在在此处创建模板
quick point I want to point out there's
我想指出的是
two different configurations for classes
两种不同的类配置
for two different types of clients so
对于两种不同类型的客户
jealous and lettuce are both two third
嫉妒和生菜都是三分之二
party Java clients that can be used to
方Java客户端，可用于
talk to to Redis and we support both of
与Redis交谈，我们都支持
them
他们
we provide connection factories for both
我们为双方提供连接工厂
of them so here we're gonna create a
他们中的一个，所以在这里我们将创建一个
rate of template which in turn injects
依次注入的模板的速率
the Redis connection factory
Redis连接工厂
one of those you know it's gonna be one
你知道的其中之一
of these implementations you know
您知道这些实现中的
automatically I think there's actually a
我自动认为实际上有一个
third one but it's just no Auto
第三，但这不是自动的
configuration for that third one so we
第三个的配置，所以我们
we support that we can configure how we
我们支持我们可以配置我们的方式
see relies the data all right so we've
see完全依赖数据，所以我们已经
got this custom raddest template let's
得到了这个自定义的raddest模板，让我们
go ahead and create our own for now just
继续并创建我们自己的
to see how it works and by the way you
看看它是如何工作的以及如何
can see down here we've got a string
可以看到这里我们有一个字符串
Redis template this string Redis
Redis模板此字符串Redis
template is just a Redis template with
模板只是一个Redis模板，
keys and values of type string right and
字符串类型right和的键和值
you can see here that they have already
您可以在这里看到他们已经
specified Eliezer's alright so this is a
指定了Eliezer的权限，所以这是一个
string sterilizer for everything right
一切都用字符串消毒器
by default however when using Redis with
默认情况下，但是当将Redis与
a with it with the JVM based application
与基于JVM的应用程序一起使用
you get Java IO serialization so the
您将获得Java IO序列化，因此
default configuration is Java JDK
默认配置为Java JDK
serialization which may or may not be
序列化可能会或可能不会
which one if using Redis entirely in the
如果完全在内部使用Redis的话
context of a homogeneous sort of Java
同类Java的上下文
based or JVM based application then it's
基于或基于JVM的应用程序
just fine but if you're using Redis with
很好，但是如果您将Redis与
multiple clients and multiple languages
多个客户和多种语言
and of course you want to you want to
当然，你想
move away from that and you can so let's
远离它，你可以让我们
let's take a look at let's take a look
让我们看一下让我们看一下
at custom configuration here okay and
在这里进行自定义配置
we'll create a new Redis template and
我们将创建一个新的Redis模板，
our with template is going to have
我们的with模板将有
custom configuration for serialization
序列化的自定义配置
so let's say that we have let's just for
所以说我们只为
now as an example we're not gonna we're
现在作为一个例子，我们不会
not gonna keep this here but let's just
不会保留在这里，但让我们
create a class of type cat and it'll be
创建一个类型为cat的类，它将是
string cat all right tell me I want to
弦猫可以告诉我我要
have a rest template that lets me work
有一个休息模板，可以让我工作
with keys and in cat name and cats right
与键，并在猫的名字和猫权利
and so the who cares about this type of
所以谁在乎这种类型的
but suffice it to say I want this to be
但是只要说我想要这个就足够了
premised to that so now I'm gonna have a
前提是现在我要有一个
read of template of type string and cat
读取string和cat类型的模板
alright and I need to now configure
好的，我现在需要配置
value sterilizers key sterilizers hash
值灭菌器关键灭菌器哈希
key services and hash bag of satellizer
卫星服务的关键服务和哈希袋
so in practice that's actually only just
所以实际上实际上只是
two in this case so it's a it's a Redis
在这种情况下，两个，这是一个Redis
sterilizer of type whatever are new and
新型的消毒器和
the disk in this case I want to just use
在这种情况下，我只想使用磁盘
a generic Jackson to JSON sterilizer
通用Jackson到JSON消毒器
serializing to or I can even say Jackson
序列化到，或者我什至可以说杰克逊
there we go
我们去
cat cat class so this is the value right
猫猫课，所以这是正确的价值
we're going to say value and this can be
我们要说的是价值，这可以是
cat if we like it doesn't really matter
猫，如果我们喜欢它并不重要
and then we want to do one for keys so
然后我们要为钥匙做一个
keys I think will just be fine with a
我认为只要一个键就可以了
string a string Cyril is ourselves Redis
西里尔是我们自己的Redis
string see what we got we have a number
字符串，看看我们得到了多少
of different options here we want the
在这里我们想要不同的选择
string right a steriliser that's the
在消毒器上串一下
type so string Redis serializer and we
输入字符串Redis序列化器，然后
don't need to see parenthesize and I
不需要看括号，我
know genera size it there's no parameter
知道一般大小，没有参数
there so the values we're going to be
在那里，我们将成为的价值观
encoded with this and the keys with that
用这个编码，用那个编码
so key cyril laser keys template dot
所以钥匙西里尔激光钥匙模板点
value sterilizer values template dot
值消毒器值模板点
hash value laser values template dot
散列值激光值模板点
hash key sterilizer keys all right so
哈希键灭菌器键好吧
we've been now you know hash values and
我们现在已经知道哈希值和
hash keys and just regular keys values
哈希键和常规键值
and we're gonna use the same as your
我们将使用与您相同的名称
lies so this is actually this is fine we
说谎，所以这实际上是很好，我们
could leave this as is but in our case
可以保持原样，但就我们而言
we're gonna express a number of
我们要表达一些
different term configurations beyond
不同的术语配置
just cats and I just want to demonstrate
只是猫，我只想示范
how this would work and of course I
这将如何工作，当然我
don't need that don't even need to be
不需要，甚至不需要
public so that would effectively replace
公开，以便有效地取代
the configuration that we have in the
我们在其中的配置
Auto config if we wanted it to but for
自动配置，如果我们想要的话
our purposes it's the prices to leave
我们的目标是离开的价格
the Auto config as is I just want you to
自动配置是我只想要你
appreciate some of the flexibility that
欣赏一些灵活性
you have here in configuring you know
你在这里配置你知道
Redis and its connectivity now this some
Redis及其连接现在有些
Auto configuration lets us work with a
自动配置使我们可以与
with a a template right we can use the
有了一个正确的模板，我们可以使用
template so let's do that we can create
模板，这样我们就可以创建
a beam of type of application writer but
一类应用程序编写器，但是
we're gonna create so many application
我们将创建很多应用程序
runners and I wanna be able to you know
跑步者，我想知道你
sort of I want to have a way of just
我有点想拥有一种
sort of setting off each application
触发每个应用程序的种类
winner so we can see the examples in the
赢家，所以我们可以在
output as we developed today so I want
我今天想要开发的输出
to create a little thing here that takes
在这里创造一件小东西
an application runner and then adapts it
应用程序运行程序，然后对其进行调整
and it prints out the title before it
然后在它前面打印出标题
runs our runner so
运行我们的跑步者
passing on that and we're gonna inject
传递下去，我们将注入
the lawn care reusing a Lombok to do
重用龙目岛做草坪护理
that right so I'll see a blog and I'll
没错，所以我会看到一个博客，然后
say log that info and then title will be
说记录信息，然后标题将是
to uppercase and there we are alright so
大写，我们还好吧
there's our titled runner and we're
有我们的冠军选手，我们
gonna do we're gonna use this a fair
我们要用这个公平吗
number of times so let's go ahead and
次数，让我们继续前进，
build our first application our first
建立我们的第一个应用程序
application using this template well
应用程序很好地使用此模板
we'll touch on a you know a fairly
我们将触及一个
under-appreciated feature which is that
被低估的特征是
Redis can support geolocation all right
Redis可以支持地理定位
so we're gonna say I want to do
所以我们要说我想做
geography here okay we're gonna create
地理在这里，我们要创建
some geography we're gonna create a
我们要创建一些地理区域
title runner geography and I'll create a
冠军亚军地理，我将创建一个
lambda here args all right
这里的lambda args好吧
now this title runner it's going to
现在这个冠军亚军
write data to the database using the
使用以下命令将数据写入数据库
this template that the straightest
这个模板最直
template that we've got here
我们在这里得到的模板
so renas template of type string and
所以renas模板的类型为string和
string it's fine for us we use the
字符串对我们来说很好，我们使用
string writers template there are t dot
字符串作家模板没有t点
and we're gonna get the opps for geo so
我们将获得地理信息系统的机会
that's going to give us the geo
这将给我们地理
operations not the hash operation it's
操作而不是哈希操作
not the ones that we can use to manage
不是我们可以用来管理的
distributed lists or values or you know
分布式列表或值，或者您知道
anything cost or primitives but instead
任何成本或原语，而是
the geo operations I'm gonna dereference
我要取消的地理操作
that stored in a variable here okay and
存储在这里的变量中
we'll use the geo or use geo here to to
我们将使用地理位置或此处的地理位置来
record a few records into the database
将一些记录记录到数据库中
so I'm going to say add and when I add a
所以我要说添加，当我添加一个
record around a city and Italy this is
记录在一个城市和意大利附近，这是
actually borrowing from the domain
实际上是从域名借来的
inside of the spring data in the side of
在弹簧数据里面
the spring data examples projects so if
春天的数据示例项目，所以如果
you go to github.com for spring -
您在春季访问github.com-
projects for spring - data - examples
春季项目-数据-示例
you'll find a number of different
您会发现许多不同的地方
options here okay so we're going to use
选项在这里好，所以我们要使用
that the point type or extreme form of
点的类型或极端形式
data Adagio and this is actually a type
数据Adagio，这实际上是一种类型
that's in the spring data framework and
在Spring数据框架中，
here I'm gonna tediously copy and paste
在这里，我要繁琐地复制和粘贴
or rather I'm just gonna type out loud
或更确切地说，我只是要大声打字
so three six one three eight nine okay
所以三六一三八九好
three 8.11 five five five
三8.11五五五
six alright and that's gonna be our okay
六个好，那将是我们的好
that adds one point two to the
将一分二加到
geolocation so it's a it's an index
地理位置，所以它是一个索引
around that key or near that key
在那个钥匙周围或附近
associate with that key for a city
与那个城市的钥匙相关联
so here the parameters if you want if
所以这里的参数如果你想
you look at this it says we're gonna add
你看这说我们要加
the key the point and then the name of
关键点，然后是名字
the member right
会员权利
I'm going to do this three more times
我要再做三遍
the second time will point to one 508
第二次指向一个508
seven two six nine three 7.5 oh two six
七二六九三7.5哦二六
six nine and this place will be called
六点九分，这个地方将被称为
cat timing you and here is the second
猫计时你，这是第二个
example the third example rather one
例如第三个例子
3.58 and that's for threes I think right
3.58，那是我认为正确的三分法
so that'll be fine and then it's a three
这样就可以了，那是三个
seven three a 7.3 one six six six seven
七三一7.3一六六六七
okay seven so I think that's right let's
好的，七个，所以我认为是对的
go let me just reconfirm here just very
走，让我在这里再次确认一下
revisit these numbers one three three
回顾这些数字一三三
six one three eight nine one three three
六一三八九一三三
six one three eight nine okay good
六一三八九好
three eight one one and then five five
三八一一然后五五
five six so three eight one one five
五六所以三八一一五
five five and that six good second set
五五和那六个好第二盘
is one 508 seven two six nine one 508
是一508七二六九一508
72-69 good three seven five oh two six
72-69好三七五哦二六
six nine three seven five oh two six six
六九三七五哦二六六
nine great next set is one three five
九大下一盘是一三五
eight three three three three
八三三三三
so that looks correct 37.3 one six six
这样看起来正确37.3一六六
seven three 7.31 667 good so we've got
七个三7.31 667好，所以我们有
now the correct data now we're going to
现在正确的数据，我们要
use that to
用它来
to create a circle I'm gonna draw a
创建一个圆圈，我要画一个
circle around one of these points and
圈出这些点之一，然后
see what falls within that circle so I'm
看看那个圆圈内的东西，所以我
gonna say new circle new point okay and
要说新圈子新观点好吧，
we'll use one three five eight three
我们将使用一三五八三
three three three seven three one six
三三三七三一六
six seven so one five five eight three
六七所以一五五八三
six six seven good and we're gonna tell
六六七好，我们要告诉
it to specify a distance of that you
它指定您的距离
know around that point using 100
用100知道这一点
kilometers so Redis geo commands dot one
公里，因此Redis地理位置命令点了一个
the other one dot distance unit
另一个点距离单位
kilometer is very good so these are our
公里非常好，所以这是我们的
circle and now we're going to use Redis
圈子，现在我们将使用Redis
to ask it what points fall within that
问它在那点上
circle so we can say geo results are
圈，所以我们可以说地理结果是
actually can just say this data or RT no
实际上只能说这些数据或RT否
sorry geo dot circle radius and we're
抱歉，地理圆点半径，我们
gonna ask it for all the things in that
会问它所有的东西
radius we're gonna say within that key
半径，我们要在该键内说
and then we'll give it a circle point
然后给它一个圆点
here and that'll give us a collection of
在这里，这将为我们提供
to your results all right so now we can
一切顺利，现在我们可以
visit each one of these geo results here
在此处访问这些地理位置结果中的每一个
and let's see it's gonna be geolocation
让我们看看它会被定位
and yeah results were gonna visit we're
是的，结果是要访问我们
gonna visit each result dot for each G
将访问每个G的每个结果点
our log info jr. to string all right so
我们的日志信息串好，这样
um we can get the content
嗯，我们可以获得内容
I suppose actually it might be even
我想实际上可能甚至
easier this to that geo results thought
这更容易使地理结果认为
get content dot for each okay so see
获取每个点的内容点，所以请参阅
logs info see it up to string let's see
日志信息将其查看为字符串，让我们来看一下
what that gives us let's run this
是什么让我们运行这个
program and see
程序看看
all right so two of those points fall
好的，所以其中两个要点
within that region Palermo and oriental
在该区域内的巴勒莫和东方
are gentle gentle sometime I get all
有时候我很温柔
right very good so that's you know a
对非常好，所以您知道
simple example but it works and you know
简单的例子，但它可以工作，你知道
obviously you wouldn't hopefully had
显然你不会希望
this hard have this hard-coded this
这个很难有这个硬编码
would be something you could load in
将是您可以加载的内容
from a GIS database or something like
从GIS数据库或类似的东西
that but a lot of possibilities here
但是这里有很多可能性
right you can do something very very
对，你可以做一些非常非常的事情
very quick work with geography here to
在这里可以非常快速地处理地理信息
support you know common geospatial kind
支持您了解常见的地理空间种类
of queries that you may may want to
您可能想要的查询
support an application now that's one
现在支持一个应用程序
common use case that's a very common use
常见用例，这是很常见的用法
cases is to to use geography to to work
案例是要利用地理来工作
as geospatial data and it's just one of
作为地理空间数据，这只是其中之一
those it's just one of those many things
这些只是众多事物之一
that Redis does it just does it well and
Redis做的很好
you while you could use post GIS or in
您可以使用GIS后发布或
the post cos world or MongoDB or
post cos世界或MongoDB或
Couchbase they both have geospatial crit
Couchbase他们都具有地理空间暴击
support as well if you've already got
支持，如果你已经有
Redis you might as well just use it
Redis你也可以使用它
right so that's a one of those many
对，所以这是其中之一
things that you can just do it out of
你可以做到的事情
the box nicely now let's talk about one
盒子好了，现在让我们谈一个
of those other things that that template
该模板的其他内容
supports right we saw the reddest
支持，我们看到了最红的
template supports are T dot hashes right
模板支持是T点散列
so hash hash Ops for hash and hash gives
因此，哈希和哈希运算的哈希运算
you a hash operations and what this lets
你做一个哈希运算，这让
you do is create a map that's associated
您要做的是创建关联的地图
with a key which is great so you have
用一个很棒的钥匙，所以你有
the ability to store basically records
基本存储记录的能力
you can store a whole whole record
您可以存储整个记录
associated with a key you could say
与您可能会说出的钥匙相关联
here's the whole you know the first name
这就是你所知道的全部名字
and last name and they email on the ID
和姓氏，他们通过ID发送电子邮件
for this username or whatever or you can
为此用户名或其他任何方式
just look it up by the ID so that's a
只需按ID查找即可，
natural thing to use to store records
用于存储记录的自然事物
and in fact we can support repositories
实际上，我们可以支持存储库
so another concept another tenant of the
所以另一个概念
spring data projects is this concept of
春季数据项目就是这个概念
a repository now a repository inspring
现在是一个存储库
data is just a convention of
数据只是
configuration of centric approach to
中心方法的配置
building queries based on the names of
根据名称建立查询
methods in interfaces and spring data
接口和弹簧数据中的方法
has a number of different
有很多不同
implementations that work with different
具有不同功能的实现
projects and these are these are meant
项目，这些都是这些
to support as much as we can but no more
尽我们最大的努力去支持
we're not trying to provide the illusion
我们不是要提供错觉
that certain things are possible for
某些事情可能
things that don't support it but we can
不支持它的东西，但我们可以
actually make basic crud style
实际上是基本的风格
repositories work with Redis so let's do
仓库与Redis一起工作，所以我们开始吧
that let's create a
让我们创建一个
a simple type here called a order and
一个简单的类型在这里称为订单和
it's going to be serializable and we
这将是可序列化的，我们
want the order to support an ID so we'll
想要订单支持ID，因此我们将
say private long ID using the spring
用春天说私人长号
framework data let's bring down a ID
框架数据让我们降低ID
type there it's gonna have an indexed
在那里输入索引
date right indexed private date when all
日期权索引私有日期
right tell you till date and we'll have
正确的告诉你直到日期，我们会
a reference to a list of line items all
对所有订单项列表的引用
right
对
so find items line items very good now
因此，现在找到非常好的订单项
this type of course we need this type
这种类型的课程，我们当然需要这种类型
class line item implements serializable
类订单项实现可序列化
and we'll come back to what that type
我们将回到那种类型
does but for now we know that this type
可以，但现在我们知道这种类型
are our type is going to support it's
我们的类型会支持它吗
gonna be persisted in the database using
将使用以下方式保留在数据库中
Redis hash functionality here we know
我们知道Redis哈希功能
that we need getters and setters so I'm
我们需要吸气剂和吸气剂，所以我
gonna say at data and all arcs
要说数据和所有弧线
constructor and no rocks constructor you
构造函数，没有岩石构造函数
don't actually need the Newark's
实际上不需要纽瓦克的
constructor for spring data it's not
Spring数据的构造函数不是
like jpoa you need it but but I want a
像jpoa，您需要它，但我想要一个
no argument constructor right because
没有参数构造函数，因为
it's just convenient these are all may
这些都可能方便
be optional but that's it good program
是可选的，但这就是好的程序
practice says if you want to have a
实践说如果你想有一个
valid a valid Li construct object you
有效的有效Li构造对象您
should learn how to be able to construct
应该学习如何能够构建
that through the constructor so maybe I
通过构造函数，所以也许我
don't need to know our constructor let's
不需要知道我们的构造函数
just leave it for now okay now I have a
现在就离开吧，好吧，我有一个
older not not quite what I wanted so
年龄不完全不是我想要的
order there and the order will have line
那里的订单，订单将有行
items and the line items will have at
项目和订单项将位于
indexed a private long order ID all
索引所有私人长期订单ID
right and will have an ID here at id
正确，并将在id处有一个ID
private long ID and that's it private
私人长ID，就是私人
string description now we want the line
字符串描述，现在我们要
items to be persisted as well nine items
要保留的项目以及九个项目
and it's gonna have all the same things
它会拥有所有相同的东西
as before now we need to create
和以前一样，我们需要创建
repositories to produce this now when we
现在，当我们生成存储库
say indexed index means that you know
说索引索引意味着您知道
it's gonna create a key it's gonna be
它会创建一个密钥，它将成为
able to I'm gonna be able to look up
我能够去抬头
this record
这个记录
by this value as I keep sort of right so
根据这个值，我保持正确的态度
it's going to create a customized if you
如果您要创建一个自定义的
create an extra slot that I can then use
创建一个我可以使用的额外插槽
to quickly reference this type by this
以此快速引用此类型
value and I wouldn't have to worry about
的价值，我不必担心
that too much but this is critical when
太多了，但是当
using Redis these types your Redis hash
使用Redis这些类型的Redis哈希
and had indexed are specific to the
并已索引到特定于
spring data Redis support the ID
spring数据Redis支持ID
annotation is generic to the spring data
注解是spring数据的通用属性
Orem abstraction the mechanism that
Orem抽象的机制
underpins this but you know we went out
支持这个，但是你知道我们出去了
of her way to make this work for Redis
她为Redis做这项工作的方式
and it's it's very valuable right it
这是非常有价值的
gives us the ability to model complex
使我们能够对复杂模型进行建模
things and still do so in an efficient
事情，并且仍然高效地这样做
way but that said we don't promise that
方式，但是那表示我们不承诺
you know we can do certain things that
你知道我们可以做某些事情
are just not reasonable for something
只是对某事不合理
like retinas which doesn't support
像不支持的视网膜
perhaps sort of the ad hoc query support
也许是临时查询支持
that you might expect for using a my
您可能期望使用我的
sequel or something like that right so
续集或类似的东西，所以
line-item got to manage line items whose
订单项必须管理其订单项
primary keys of type long and interface
long类型和接口的主键
order repository it's going to extend
订单存储库将要扩展
crud repository whose payload of type is
负载类型为
order and ID is long alright
订单和ID好吗
so there are two types now maybe I want
所以现在可能有两种类型
to have a custom finder method here
在这里有一个自定义查找器方法
let's say I want to do collection you
假设我想收集你
know let's say I want to find a an order
知道，假设我想找到订单
by its date fine by when right so date D
在其日期之前罚款，在适当的时候日期D
and I can do that that works actually
我可以做到这一点实际上
just fine with with our Redis
与我们的Redis一起很好
abstraction here so let's say we want to
这里说抽象，我们想
create some data we have to create an
创建一些数据，我们必须创建一个
application runner that supports this
支持此功能的应用程序运行程序
data so red is so repositories and
如此红的数据是如此的存储库，
what's a return titled runner
什么叫亚军
repositories args and we'll go ahead and
存储库args，我们将继续
run that and the repository we're gonna
运行它，我们要去的仓库
write some data to the database we're
向我们写入一些数据到数据库
gonna have a couple of Records we're
我们将会有几张唱片
going to see well first so I need to
首先要看清楚，所以我需要
create an order ID so long order ID and
创建订单ID，以便订单ID长
I need to generate a ID all right it's
我需要生成一个ID
all quite a convenience method here
都在这里很方便
because I'm going to do this a lot today
因为我今天要做很多
so we'll say
所以我们会说
long temp equals new random dot next
长温度等于下一个新的随机点
long and that may be negative so I'm
很长，可能是负面的，所以我
going to say math dot max temp or temp
会说数学点最高温度或最高温度
times negative one and I'll return that
负数倍，我将退还
so there's our generated ID and what I
所以有我们生成的ID和我
want to do is I want to create a few
想做的就是我要创建一些
different line items and I'll save those
不同的订单项，我将保存
first so arrays dot as list new line
首先，数组点作为列表新行
item order ID generate ID and we're
物料订单ID生成ID，我们
going to call this a plunger for example
例如将其称为柱塞
and a new line item will be order ID
一个新的订单项将是订单ID
generate ID a soup and a new line item
生成ID，汤和新订单项
will be order ID generate ID and you
将是订单ID生成ID，您
know what's a good one a coffee mug sure
知道什么是好咖啡
all right so now we've got these types
好吧，现在我们有了这些类型
got these records I'm going to save to
得到了这些记录，我将保存到
the day base so so we need to actually
因此，我们需要实际
visit each one and then save them so I'm
拜访每个人，然后保存它们，所以我
gonna say item list dot stream dot map
要说项目列表点流点图
and a pass in the line item repository
和订单项存储库中的通行证
so let's do that here so line item
所以我们在这里做这样的订单项
repository and here I'll say repository
存储库，在这里我将说存储库
dot save it and it is of course the
点保存它，它当然是
generic there replace it with a method
通用那里用一种方法代替它
of reference if we want and then we need
参考，如果我们想要，那么我们需要
to subscribe so we need to actually
订阅，所以我们需要实际
visit each record that comes back and
访问返回的每条记录，
we'll say for each L I system out I
我们将针对每个LI系统说
guess we can just use log right no
猜猜我们可以直接使用日志否
problem
问题
li so I lined up to string very good
李，所以我排队很不错
look at that we've got now these
看看我们现在有了这些
different records and that should work
不同的记录，应该工作
let's go ahead and run this to see what
让我们继续运行此命令，看看有什么
we get
我们得到
okay so it's those the three records
好的，那是那三个记录
after they've been saved now let's
保存完之后，让我们
create the order order equals new order
创建订单等于新订单
here the order ID will pass that
在这里，订单ID将通过
indirectly the new date will be this one
间接地，新日期将是这个日期
right here and Elena the item list will
就在这里，埃琳娜，物品清单
be this and now we're going to save this
就是这个，现在我们要保存这个
as well we're gonna say to inject the
我们也要说注入
order repository so order repository and
订单存储库，因此订单存储库和
I guess I can rename this to line item
我想我可以将其重命名为订单项
repository and I'll say order repository
仓库，我会说订单仓库
dot save order and that will give us a
点保存命令，这将给我们一个
result that's been saved in the database
结果已保存在数据库中
and we can then inspect it we can say
然后我们可以检查它，我们可以说
order repository dot find by when where
订单库点查找时间
order dot get win so this should return
订单点获得胜利，所以这应该返回
if everything goes to plan retreat you
如果一切按计划进行，务虚会
know found and you know it's gonna
知道找到了，你知道它将
return a collection I suppose or we
返回我想的集合，或者我们
couldn't even do an optional if we want
如果我们想甚至不能做一个可选的
to we could have said optional of T find
我们本可以说T find的可选
by whatever if we know there's only one
如果我们知道只有一个
or zero so there we go so we've got that
或零，所以我们走了，所以我们得到了
now and let's just visit those records
现在，让我们访问这些记录
so we'll say found out for each o log
因此，我们将说每个日志都找到了
dot info found out to string alright so
点信息找到字符串好所以
I'm visiting the data that's coming back
我正在访问返回的数据
from the database after I'm querying it
我查询完数据库后
after I've written it to the database so
将其写入数据库后，
I'm gonna run the there we go so he
我要跑那我们去，所以他
wrote it to the database we found it got
把它写到数据库中，我们发现它
this record back and of course we got
这个记录回来了，我们当然得到了
the reference to line items therein
对其中订单项的引用
right so the description is the plunger
对，所以描述是柱塞
the soup and the coffee mug all that
汤和咖啡杯
it's just been done for us automatically
它只是为我们自动完成的
now if we look at what's happening
现在，如果我们看看发生了什么
behind the scenes here and now if you
如果你现在在这里幕后
can see it's actually created a whole
可以看到它实际上是一个整体
schema that's managing all of this for
用于管理所有这些的模式
me right it's just managing it for me I
我是对的，只是为我管理
don't have to worry about it and it it's
不必担心，它是
got indexes it's got the a relationships
有索引，有关系
it's got all these keys orders when etc
当等时所有这些按键命令
as all as being done for us so we don't
就像为我们所做的一样，所以我们不
have to worry about you know any of this
不必担心你知道这一切
kind of complicated stuff riddance is
一种复杂的东西摆脱是
perfectly happy to do it it's just that
很高兴做到这一点
there's a little bit of
有一点
manual assembly required here and the
此处需要手动组装以及
spring data abstraction does that work
Spring数据抽象可以做到这一点
for us so that we can now get the best
为我们，以便我们现在可以得到最好的
use out of Redis here okay all right so
在这里使用Redis可以，所以
that's a very simple example that's just
这是一个非常简单的例子
a we're taking we're using hashes behind
一个我们正在使用我们在后面使用哈希
the scenes right this is actually
对的场景这实际上是
fundamentally turning into things like
从根本上变成
hashes and and and keys and values it's
散列和与以及键和值是
using the fundamental atoms of Redis but
使用Redis的基本原子，但是
it's doing something very sophisticated
它做的事情非常复杂
on top which allows us to focus on a
最重要的是，我们可以专注于
higher-order business logic concerns so
高阶业务逻辑问题
the next thing that we want to focus on
接下来我们要关注的是
when we look at and our little tour here
当我们看着和我们的小游览
of Venice is a using it for
的威尼斯是用它来
publish/subscribe right this is a common
发布/订阅权这是很常见的
use case I want to pub I want to
我想发布的用例
communicate from one note to another
从一个音符传达到另一个音符
using some sort of middleware where I
在我使用某种中间件的地方
could of course install Apache Kafka or
当然可以安装Apache Kafka或
RabbitMQ and these are growth these are
RabbitMQ，这些都是增长，
both fine choices maybe even a JMS
两者都是不错的选择，甚至是JMS
broker although there are reasons why
经纪人，尽管有原因
you might want to avoid that last one
您可能要避免最后一个
but Redis is actually you know it's fine
但是Redis实际上你知道这很好
it's it's not it's not it's not the most
是不是不是不是不是最多
feature full message broker in the
功能完整的消息代理
business but if you've already got it
业务，但如果您已经掌握了
installed and you're trying to do simple
已安装，而您尝试做的简单
pub/sub then this might be all you need
pub / sub，那么这可能就是您所需要的
especially if you're just doing a status
特别是如果您只是在做一个状态
update or it's it's fine that you might
更新或者就可以了
lose a message here in there right if
如果在这里失去信息
you're trying to do finance transactions
您正在尝试进行金融交易
then yeah okay probably a probably
那好吧，大概
better to use something like rabbitmq or
最好使用Rabbitmq或
Kafka right but here we're just going
卡夫卡没错，但我们要走了
okay we're gonna you know let's suppose
好吧，我们会知道的
we have a chat right and we're one of
我们有聊天权，我们是其中之一
our status notifications or you know
我们的状态通知，或者您知道
presidents awareness or something like
总统的意识或类似的东西
that this is a perfectly fine choice
这是一个完美的选择
because it's gonna be in memory it's
因为它会在记忆中
gonna be lightning-fast and the clients
会闪电般飞速前进，客户
are gonna be able to you know publish
将能够让您知道发布
messages to a topic which is actually
消息实际上是一个主题
just a key and with us a queue behind
只是一把钥匙，而我们却排在后面
the scenes and and then they can consume
场景，然后它们可以消耗
it so we actually have it support for
所以我们实际上有它的支持
this in spring as well so let's create
春季也是如此，让我们来创建
am a an application that sends a message
是一个发送消息的应用程序
so here I'm going to create an
所以在这里我要创建一个
application writer being an application
应用程序编写者是一个应用程序
runner pub/sub and we're gonna return a
跑步者发布者/订阅者，我们将返回一个
titled so publish sub scribe
标题为pubscribe subscribe
okay and scribe there we go
好吧，抄写到那里去
args and we'll use this
args，我们将使用它
publish/subscribe endpoint use this
发布/订阅端点使用此
runner to now send a message and that's
跑步者现在要发送一条消息，那就是
that's the easy part
那是容易的部分
I mean both both producer and consumer
我的意思是生产者和消费者
are easy really but I'm gonna use the
真的很容易，但我要使用
rest template here so write it in a
在这里休息模板，所以写在
rightist template of type string and
字符串类型的右派模板和
string RT and we're gonna say R T dot
字符串RT，我们要说RT点
convert and send and we're gonna create
转换并发送，我们将创建
a channel here a shared channel a topic
此处的频道共享频道主题
so private final string topic I guess
所以我猜私有的最终字符串主题
whatever who cares chat okay and I'm
无论谁在乎聊天好吧，我
gonna say that I'm gonna send a message
要说我要发信息
to this topic so top pick and we can
这个话题，所以我们可以选择
just you know there okay and the message
只是你知道那里好，并且消息
I'm going to send is any arbitrary
我要发送的是任意的
message in here it could be you know it
这里的消息可能是您知道的
could be um json encoded it could be a
可能是json编码，可能是
string it could be whatever you want so
字符串它可以是您想要的任何东西
but we're relying on the default string
但是我们依赖默认字符串
sterilization here so i'm just gonna
在这里消毒，我要
send a string hello world at instant dot
在即时点发送字符串你好世界
now dot to string alright so I'm sending
现在点到字符串好了，所以我要发送
a timing coded message and now I need to
时间编码的消息，现在我需要
consume that message now I could spit up
消耗掉那条消息现在我可以吐了
another note and it would be very easy
另一个音符，这将非常容易
but since we already understand how that
但是既然我们已经了解了
would work and I want to save myself
会工作，我想救自己
some typing time I'm gonna go ahead and
一些打字时间，我要继续
create a message listener consumer here
在此处创建消息侦听器使用者
in the and the same the same note so I'm
在相同的音符中，所以我
doing I'm sending a message into Redis
我正在向Redis发送消息
and it's gonna be delivered right back
它会马上被送回来
to the same node which is acting as a
到同一个节点
client so it's actually it's making the
客户，所以实际上是
same network hops as it would word it
与其说的话一样的网络跳数
you know weren't to actually be to give
你知道不是真的要付出
to given projects but I just want to
给定的项目，但我只想
demonstrate how this works okay so
演示这是如何工作的，这样
that's now create a message listener
现在创建一个消息监听器
that's going to respond to messages and
这将响应消息，
then in spring we've had we have this
然后在春天，我们有了这个
concept of a message listener container
消息侦听器容器的概念
right so a message listener container
对，所以消息侦听器容器
I'm gonna use the rest that Redis
我要用剩下的Redis
message listener container and this
消息监听器容器和这个
reddit reddit message listener container
reddit reddit消息监听器容器
needs a witness
需要一个证人
it needs a message listener so let's
它需要一个消息监听器，所以让我们
create the Redis message there's our
创建Redis消息，这是我们的
container
容器
like so and the MLC needs a connection
像这样，MLC需要连接
factory of course oh well inject the
工厂当然可以注入
Redis connection factory alright and I
Redis连接工厂很好，我
will say CF and we'll say m LLC dot we
会说CF，我们会说m LLC点
need we didn't need a message listener
需要我们不需要消息监听器
alright so we need to do that as well
好吧，所以我们也需要这样做
and the the message listener will be ml
消息侦听器将是ml
we'll come back to that in a second and
我们将在稍后再讨论
then we need a pattern topic so I'm
那么我们需要一个模式主题
gonna tell it to use this dot topic
要告诉它使用这个点主题
right same as before and that's it
和以前一样就这样
that's the MLC itself but we need the
那是MLC本身，但我们需要
message listener so let's do that that's
消息监听器，让我们做到这一点
the easy bit and so ml equals new
容易一点，所以毫升等于新的
message that's not a very simple
消息不是很简单
interface and here we're going to take
界面，在这里我们将采取
the data from the pain wood and just log
来自痛苦的木头的数据，只是记录
it out right just just confirm that it's
只是确认它是
as we expected it to be and and
正如我们期望的那样
enumerate the value all right so let's
枚举值好吧，让我们
let's do that here we're gonna say
让我们在这里做，我们要说
string string equals a new string
字符串字符串等于新字符串
message dot get body
消息点获取正文
those are bytes that come in and we want
这些是进来的字节，我们想要
to log it out so long that info new
登出很长时间，以至于没有新信息
message or message from ok and it'll be
消息或来自OK的消息，它将是
this dot topic or the topic
这个点主题或主题
okay STR very cool now we can use that
好的STR非常酷，现在我们可以使用它了
messagelistener all right
留言者可以吗
good replace it with a lambda so they
好用lambda代替它，所以他们
recall there we go so there's our mrs.
回想一下，我们去了，所以有我们的太太。
position container and our incoming
位置容器和我们的进货
messages and we can now read the data
消息，我们现在可以读取数据
let's let's let's see what happens so
让我们让我们看看会发生什么
let's go ahead and run this now keep in
让我们继续运行，现在继续
mind this message is going to be
请注意，此消息将是
received asynchronously out-of-band
带外异步接收
so we're gonna see the header for
所以我们将看到标题
publish/subscribe be printed and it
发布/订阅并打印
might actually let's say
也许可以说
publish/subscribe gets printed where's
发布/订阅在哪里打印
the result found did I do something
结果发现我做了什么
wrong message listener container
错误的消息侦听器容器
messagelistener
留言者
message
信息
they turn the container returned that I
他们打开容器，我回来了
don't see it doing uh I see it doing
没有看到它在做，我看到它在做
this don't I so there's they published
这不是我，所以他们发表了
there is a publish/subscribe in point
有一个发布/订阅点
and then I do it the wrong way around
然后我做错了
convert and send to the topic hello
转换并发送给主题你好
world
世界
yeah that looks right doesn't it so how
是的，看起来不错，不是吗
is it
是吗
I'm missing something obvious clearly
我明显缺少明显的东西
publish/subscribe
发布/订阅
and the topic
和主题
let's say it's called chat log that info
假设该信息称为聊天记录
can we try this again this time with the
我们这次可以再试一次吗
debugger let's see what we get
调试器让我们看看我们得到了什么
it's not quite working the way I
这不是我的工作方式
expected it to so let me see it's a
期待它，所以让我看看这是一个
message this in a container Renaissance
在容器中传送此消息文艺复兴
Center yeah
是啊
there is the name of the bean I was some
我有一些豆的名字
other beam is conflicting without bean
没有豆，其他光束发生冲突
type so I renamed it to listener and I
输入，所以我将其重命名为监听器，然后
got message from chat hello world blah
收到来自您好聊天世界的消息等等
blah blah okay so that actually worked
等等等等好，这样才能真正起作用
that was a I was a mysterious one so
那是一个我是一个神秘的人，所以
they were going I guess we just learned
他们要走了，我想我们刚刚学会了
something new don't use the name and
新的东西不要使用名称和
that I had just had before to name your
我刚刚曾经给你起名字
container but once you do this once
容器，但是一旦执行一次
you've changed it from that it'll work
您已经更改了它，它将起作用
so here we go we have a message there's
所以在这里，我们有一个消息，
no container that's responding or that
没有响应的容器
receives the incoming message and it can
收到传入的消息，它可以
do something with it so now you can do
用它做点什么，所以现在你可以做
all sorts of interesting things here you
这里有各种各样有趣的事情
could create topics based on you know
可以根据您的了解创建主题
okay so this thing here is a topic of
好吧，这是这里的话题
some sort you could create a topic that
您可以创建某种主题
has a unique key that only one producer
有一个唯一的密钥，只有一个生产者
and consumer would agree on you can do
消费者会同意您可以做到的
broadcast them you can do all sorts of
广播他们，你可以做各种各样的
things you know here with this basic
您在这里基本了解的事情
messaging primitive right so this is yet
消息传递原语正确，所以到目前为止
another thing that's a kind of just
另一件事只是
supported out of the box it's a
开箱即用的支持
little-known feature of Redis that I
Redis鲜为人知的功能
hope you'll take advantage of right we
希望您能利用我们的权利
also support using Redis for keys and
还支持将Redis用于密钥和
values naturally and there's a lot of
自然地重视价值，并且有很多
different places where you would want to
您想在不同的地方
do that including in caching right so
做到这一点，包括缓存，这样
when you cache data let me move this
当您缓存数据时，让我移动它
code to the top of the code page there
代码到代码页顶部
there we are and what we want to do is
我们在那里，我们要做的是
want to cache data that we've you know
想缓存我们知道的数据
that we've created that perhaps
我们创造的也许
expensive to arrive at so let's say that
到达很昂贵，所以可以说
enable caching at the right top here and
启用此处右上方的缓存，然后
so an able caching and in our build you
如此强大的缓存能力，在我们的构建中，您
will see that we have here in the build
会看到我们在构建中
we have the spring data Redis dependency
我们有spring数据Redis依赖
and that dependency has a a cache
并且该依赖项具有一个缓存
manager abstraction so it's gonna work
经理抽象，所以它会工作
in conjunction with the at enable
与at enable结合使用
caching annotation and if we're it to do
缓存注释，如果我们要这样做
its work it's going to need a cache
它的工作将需要一个缓存
manager implementation and we can
经理实施，我们可以
configure that fairly easily so let's do
相当容易地配置，让我们做
that here we'll say that bean I guess we
在这里我们会说那个豆我想我们
can do it here here at bean cache
可以在这里在bean缓存中做到这一点
manager Redis cache you know okay and
经理Redis缓存，您知道还可以，
that's will create the cache manager and
这将创建缓存管理器，
we're gonna say return new we're gonna
我们要说返回新的我们要
use the rest cache manager builder
使用其余的高速缓存管理器构建器
method here so - cache manager
方法在这里-缓存管理器
dot that builder I'm gonna inject the
点，我要注入的建设者
witness connection factory will say
见证连接工厂会说
builder dot CF that build alright so
生成器点CF可以正常构建
there's our Redis cache manager
有我们的Redis缓存管理器
abstraction implementation and now we
抽象实现，现在我们
can create something stateful that has
可以创建有状态的东西
that's protect potentially performant
保护潜在的表演者
and expensive and we want to be able to
和昂贵，我们希望能够
memorize or remember the results of a
记住或记住结果
method invocation so I'm not gonna do no
方法调用，所以我不会做不
the goal here is not to do a whole
这里的目标不是做一个整体
introduction to the cache manager
缓存管理器简介
abstraction although you should
抽象虽然你应该
absolutely look into it but instead I
绝对会研究它，但是我
want to create you know I want to
想创建你知道我想
demonstrate how this works seamlessly
演示这是如何无缝进行的
with Redis so I'm gonna create a order
与Redis合作，所以我要创建一个订单
service let's just say okay so an order
服务，让我们说好吧，所以订购
service and this order service is going
服务，此订单服务正在进行
to be
成为
cashable so I'm gonna support caching
可兑现的，所以我要支持缓存
results that come back from this method
从此方法返回的结果
so public order by ID looking up the ID
因此，通过ID查找公共秩序ID
here I'm going to say add cacheable and
这里我要说的是添加可缓存的
we're gonna say well you know order by
我们要说的很好，您知道订购者
ID so it'll look up the records from
ID，以便从中查找记录
this method it'll take up there it'll
这种方法会占用那里
look up and look up the lookup and Redis
查找并查找查找和Redis
any of the data that comes from this let
任何来自此的数据
me try that again
我再试一次
when you call this method it's gonna see
当您调用此方法时，它将看到
first of all if there's a results
首先，如果有结果
already stored in the in the record in
已经存储在记录中
the database with this key and another
具有此键和另一个的数据库
key that's you know a combination of key
你知道的钥匙组合
based on this name here and the
根据此处的名称以及
arguments to the method of location and
定位方法的参数和
there are arguments that either
有争论
sanitation's that you can use to to
您可以用来清洁卫生
control you know which which keys should
控制您知道哪个键应该
be used and which which which
使用哪个
invocations should be used to evict data
调用应用于逐出数据
from that from the from the cache but
从缓存中
let's just assume that we want every
让我们假设我们想要每一个
argument there to contribute to the key
在那里争论有助于关键
that is then used to return this
然后用来返回这个
resolved result so now let's say return
解决的结果，所以现在让我们说返回
new order passing in the ID and a new
新订单传递ID和新订单
day tune or just passing empty a list of
日间调整或只是空列表
line items there now what we're gonna do
订单项现在我们要做的是
is we're going to create a artificial
是我们要创造一个人造的
sleep so it'll take a second to solve a
睡觉，所以需要一秒钟来解决
second if somebody wants to call this
如果有人想打电话给第二
without having having it already in the
却没有
cache and then otherwise let's just make
缓存，然后让我们
it ten seconds and it's actually
十秒钟，实际上
perceptible
可察觉的
okay so and then otherwise uh it'll just
好吧，然后否则，呃
go straight to thinking straight to our
直接思考我们
Arbutus cash okay so let's say at log
杨梅现金还可以，所以在日志中说
and we'll say well that error info I
我们会说好错误信息
guess exception actually doesn't even
猜测异常实际上甚至没有
matter was just to do throw new running
只是要做新的事情
time exception all right it's all right
时间例外没事吧
even care about this don't even need the
甚至在乎这个都不需要
logs so we're creating an artifact we're
日志，因此我们正在创建工件
just returning the result to cares about
只是将结果返回到关心
the result but we want to want to induce
结果，但我们想诱导
that artificial sleep to make sure that
人工睡眠以确保
we can see how fast it's going so now
我们可以看到它进行的速度有多快
let's call that order service from a
让我们从
repository from a runner and prove that
跑步者的资料库，并证明
it's working so it's got a new beam of
它正在工作，所以有了新的一束光芒
that specific application runner so
该特定的应用程序运行程序
cache and we'll use this order service
缓存，我们将使用此订单服务
which has been created for us order what
为我们创建的订单
did I save it as order service order
我将其保存为订单服务订单吗
service I am NOT going great with that
服务我做得不好
word today so order service and titled
今天的单词，所以订购服务和标题
caching a good so there's this and in
缓存好东西，所以有这个
the in the order service we're gonna
在订单服务中，我们将
call the method so we're gonna do so a
调用该方法，所以我们将这样做
number of different times so what I'm
不同的时间数，所以我是
going to do is I'm going to measure each
我要做的是测量每个
invocation
调用
so we'll say runnable are how we're
所以我们会说可运行的
gonna do this what's the easiest way to
要做到这一点，最简单的方法是
do this we can create a method to save
为此，我们可以创建一种保存方法
the let's see class
让我们看课
yeah
是的
private long measure and we're gonna
私人长措施，我们要
take a runnable are and we will save the
采取一个可运行的是，我们将保存
current time
当前时间
so start equal system current time Milly
所以开始等于系统当前时间Milly
long stop equals system that current
多头止损等于当前系统
time mini and we're going to run our dat
迷你时间，我们将运行我们的数据
run and
运行并
what is that about private okay and
那私人好吗？
we're going to turn return stop - start
我们要转身返回停止-开始
so that's the measure method there and
这就是那里的测量方法
we're gonna measure some runner bulls
我们要测量一些亚军
and the runnable is gonna be measure
可以衡量的是
it's gonna be this so I'm going to say
就是这样，我要说
run order service dot by ID 1l all right
可以通过ID 1l运行订单服务点
and so now I'm going to print out the
所以现在我要打印出
timings for that so let's say we have
这样的时机，让我们说我们有
log that info first and we'll print out
首先记录该信息，我们将打印出
measure okay so two times two and three
可以，所以两次，两次，三次
times so we'll have now a three
次，所以我们现在有三个
invocations of the same basic thing it's
相同基本事物的调用
gonna run this invocation each time and
每次都会运行此调用，
and we'll see the results hopefully all
我们希望会看到所有结果
right so we'll say you know call this
对，所以我们会说你知道叫这个
and then show us what we got so now
然后告诉我们我们现在得到了什么
let's see why is this still upset oh
让我们看看为什么这仍然令人沮丧哦
this because the M inspection disable
这是因为M检查禁用
that inspection
那个检查
okay now let's go ahead and run this
好吧，现在让我们继续运行
again this time we're gonna run it's
这次我们要再次运行它
gonna be called caching while caching
缓存时称为缓存
the same lookup it the first time it
第一次相同的查询
should take whatever we said ten seconds
我们应该说十秒钟
so it's calling caching taking its
所以它称缓存为
tedious amount of time here of course
当然这里很乏味的时间
there is also the first time it took ten
也是第一次花了十
thousand and nine milliseconds
一千零九毫秒
ten seconds and nine mils late so the
迟了十秒零九密耳，所以
actual access on the first time is nine
第一次实际访问是9
milliseconds the second time it took two
第二次花了毫秒
milliseconds in the third time took one
第三次以毫秒为单位
millisecond or you know less then so
毫秒，或者您知道的那么少
this is this could actually be
这可能实际上是
nanosecond granularity at this point I
纳秒级粒度I
don't know I'm just got it
不知道我就知道了
it's giving us the it's rounding up of
它给我们的是四舍五入
course right so the point is we have the
当然正确，所以重点是我们有
ability to go really quickly for using
能够真正快速使用的能力
memoization right and we get that for
记忆权，我们得到
free and behind the scenes you know if
自由和幕后，你知道是否
we look at this keys we have invocation
我们看看这个键，我们有调用
it's based on IDs in there so let's see
它基于其中的ID，所以让我们看看
I'm not even sure if I can spot the EM
我什至不确定我是否能发现EM
it's about the invocation the
这是关于调用
incantation that's being used to make
用来制造的咒语
that call
那个电话
alright so orders oh and if it's that
好吧，命令哦，如果是那样
one anyway that's being done for us
无论如何正在为我们做
automatic oh they're just ordered by the
自动哦，他们只是由
one right so that's the incantation and
一种权利，那就是咒语
if we look at that wait if you look at
如果我们看着那等一下，如果你看着
that value orders okay so keys and
值顺序好吗，所以键和
get value that's
获得价值
read
读
okay so we're trying to get the value
好吧，所以我们试图获得价值
for a key and if I'm honest I don't know
一把钥匙，如果我说实话我不知道
the command that you're supposed to use
您应该使用的命令
them in the rid of CLI I just always do
他们摆脱了CLI，我总是会做
it from from Springs so is it get key
它来自Springs，所以它是关键吗
let's try and get something okay there
让我们在那里尝试一下
we go that make sense so paste there you
我们说的有意义，所以贴在你那里
go so there's the Java cos encoding of
去，所以有Java cos编码
that object again you can use a custom
再次使用该对象，您可以使用自定义
sterilizer but you can see it's it's got
消毒器，但您可以看到它已经
the same information that we need
我们需要的相同信息
there's the order and aligned items and
有订单和对齐的项目，
you know all the bits that are required
你知道所有需要的位
to to make this work the Java util date
使这项工作成为Java util日期
all that stuff is there all right okay
所有的东西都好吧
so there's the memoized version of the
所以有记忆的版本
the record and that would work you know
记录，那会起作用的，你知道
serialization issues notwithstanding
尽管有序列化问题
that would work across multiple virtual
可以跨多个虚拟
machines as well so if if we have ten
机器，如果我们有十台
different applications web application
不同的应用程序Web应用程序
and they're out there making calls to
他们在那里打电话给
this order service and one client makes
这个订单服务和一个客户
a call on one web service one one
一个Web服务上的通话一个
application instance then other clients
应用程序实例，然后是其他客户端
accessing the same record another
访问同一条记录
application instances would benefit from
应用程序实例将从中受益
that lookup and of course you could have
查找，当然你可以有
cache evict annotations to evict you can
缓存逐出注释可以逐出
say public void update long ID and you
说public void更新长ID，而您
can say you know cached evict this
可以说您知道已将其逐出
record based on this this method call so
根据此方法调用记录
we would actually invalidate the record
我们实际上会使记录无效
in the repository based on the the call
根据调用在存储库中
all right so now speaking of web another
好的，所以现在谈到网络
very logical sort of use case for for a
非常合乎逻辑的用例
cash like renas is to use it for a
像雷纳斯这样的现金就是用它来
session storage right so let's bring
会话存储权，让我们带上
that application backups readiness
应用程序备份就绪
application we've got this application
应用程序，我们有这个应用程序
now running and the application is
现在正在运行，该应用程序正在
running and we've got um you know no
跑步，我们有嗯，你不知道
WebM point right now so let's go ahead
WebM现在指向，让我们继续吧
and do that we're gonna build a simple
并做到这一点，我们将建立一个简单的
web endpoint that's gonna use the HTTP
将使用HTTP的网络端点
session so we'll say what do I want to
会议，所以我们会说我想做什么
write I can do it in here let's say
写我可以在这里说
class session you know cart session
你知道的课程
controller alright and this is going to
控制器好，这将
be a logged and spring MVC controller
成为已记录的Spring MVC控制器
that's going to have a session attribute
这将具有一个会话属性
called cart and we'll come back to that
叫做购物车，我们将返回
in a second
一秒钟
and the data we're gonna create a model
以及我们要创建的数据
attribute so what's gonna happen is
属性，所以会发生的是
we're gonna we're gonna return a
我们要返回一个
shopping cart
购物车
okay so class like so and the shopping
好吧，像这样的阶级和购物
cart will have a collection of orders
购物车将有一个订单集合
orders and this has to be all C reliable
订单，这必须是所有C可靠的
so you should probably use a little bit
所以你应该使用一点
more care here but I'm gonna be using a
这里需要更多的照顾，但我要使用
very simple and a very simple sort of
非常简单，非常简单
thread naive approach here so I'm going
线程天真的方法在这里，所以我要
to say public void and order and I use
说公共无效和秩序，我用
an order object here so order order
这里的订单对象
and this orders dot to add order good
这个订单点加订单好
and I'm gonna have another endpoint here
我将在这里有另一个终点
that returns a collection of order get
返回订单的集合get
orders all right let's return this dot
命令好吧，让我们返回这个点
orders dot there we go so that's my very
订单点到那里，所以这是我非常
simple shopping cart and we want the
简单的购物车，我们想要
shopping cart to be persistent so I'm
购物车要持久，所以我
gonna make it serializable as well okay
还要使其可序列化
and we want to support where's my for
我们想支持我的工作
matter on that expands part of the
的问题扩大了一部分
problem so now let me confirm that's
问题，现在让我确认
working good all right so there's that
一切都很好，所以
this is session attributes good so
这是会话属性，所以
what's going to happen is when this
将会发生什么事
spring MVC controller gets loaded
Spring MVC控制器被加载
there's gonna be certain endpoints here
这里会有某些终点
that are gonna look for a cart and then
会寻找一辆手推车，然后
look for the cart in the session if they
如果他们在会话中寻找购物车
don't find it they're gonna have to
找不到它们，他们将不得不
create a brand new object that they can
创建一个他们可以
use as a backing beam for data that's
用作数据的支撑
gonna be created in the lifecycle of one
将在一个人的生命周期中被创造
is handler methods so it's gonna look to
是处理程序方法，因此它将
a model attribute method on the
模型属性方法
controller to vend a new instance of
出售新实例的控制器
that of that cart so a return new
那辆车的东西，所以回来了
shopping cart so this is gonna be empty
购物车，所以这将是空的
I'm gonna log you know producing or
我要记录你知道的生产或
creating new cart alright I'm going to
创建新的购物车好了，我要去
log that
记录
and then I'm gonna use them I say that's
然后我要使用它们，我说那是
create an in point here called orders
在此处创建一个定单，称为订单
that you know dot Redis or whatever just
你知道点Redis或其他任何东西
call it with orders if you want that's
用命令叫它，如果你想
gonna return an HTML page rendered with
将要返回的HTML页面
time and if and that's gonna inject this
时间，如果并且那将注入这个
model attributes a model attribute cart
模型属性模型属性购物车
and it'll be shopping cart so a shopping
这将是购物车，所以购物
cart to cart and we're gonna create a
购物车到购物车，我们将创建一个
model lets bring me some model to render
模型让我带一些模型来渲染
the the view here and the model is just
这里的视图和模型只是
gonna have some data in it mono add
里面会有一些数据
attribute orders and it'll be cart died
属性订单，它将被购物车杀死
get order so this what we're gonna do is
得到订单，所以我们要做的是
whenever somebody goes to this endpoint
每当有人去这个终点
we're gonna add a new order and we're
我们要添加一个新订单，我们
gonna have a private atomic private
将有一个私人原子私人
atomic long right so private final
原子长权，所以私人决赛
atomic long new atomic long and I call
原子长新原子长我叫
this IDs and we'll add the order here
这个ID，我们将在这里添加订单
like so we'll say ID dot increment and
就像这样，我们将说ID点增量和
get new date and collections dot empty
获取新日期，收藏集为空
list so when I add a new record each
列出，以便当我分别添加新记录时
time and then render a view called
时间，然后渲染一个名为
orders that hasn't activated them in the
尚未激活的订单
view called orders that we're going to
查看我们要去的被叫定单
iterate in the view so to review
在视图中进行迭代，以便进行审查
somebody's gonna call this endpoint
有人将这个端点称为
we're going to add a new record to the
我们将向
cart in the session if the cart if the
会话中的购物车
session doesn't if the record doesn't
如果记录不存在，会话也不会
exist in the session then it's gonna
存在于会话中，然后它将
call this model attribute method and
将此模型属性方法称为
then it's gonna it's gonna use that -
然后就可以使用它-
it's gonna be injected here as a
它会以一种
parameter and I'm gonna add a new record
参数，我要添加一条新记录
so over time given the same session we
因此，随着时间的推移，我们进行了相同的会话
should see an increasing number of
应该看到越来越多的
orders in the cart but if you start a
购物车中的订单，但如果您开始
new session it's just it should be set
新的会话，只是应该设置
back to zero and we should see it saying
回到零，我们应该看到它说
creating a new cart right so first time
马上创建一个新的购物车
it'll it'll call that okay now we need a
好吧，现在我们需要一个
template some sort of view so this is
模板某种视图，所以这是
why I added time they fear so source
为什么我加时间他们害怕所以来源
main resources templates I'm gonna
我将要使用的主要资源模板
create a file here called orders dot
在此处创建一个名为订单点的文件
HTML and the orders that HTML file we're
HTML和HTML文件的顺序
just gonna we're just gonna you know I
只是我们要你知道我
won't I'll spare you I'll spare you all
我不会饶你的我会饶大家的
this live coding there so desktop
这个实时编码在那里，所以桌面
Redis source resources templates or to
Redis源资源模板或
study HTML clipboard good man so there's
学习HTML剪贴板好人，所以
that so very very simple Redis orders
非常非常简单的Redis命令
right right as orders and what we do is
是正确的命令，我们要做的是
want to render a div element but rather
想渲染一个div元素，而是
we're gonna render two spans for every
我们将为每个渲染两个范围
order Oh in the orders I attribute from
我从中归属的订单中的订单哦
the view Evan model rather so when a
查看Evan模型时，
dereference the ID and the when
取消引用ID和何时
attribute right in the order so I think
属性顺序正确，所以我认为
that should be in it the only thing we
那应该是我们唯一的东西
need to do now is to enable spring
现在需要做的是启用弹簧
sessions spring session is the facility
春季会议是设施
that lets us swap out the HTTP servlet
让我们换出HTTP Servlet
session and replace it with with a
会话并将其替换为
pluggable session store of our choice
我们选择的可插入会话存储
and here we're using Venice we could use
在这里，我们正在使用威尼斯，我们可以使用
the H cache or in memory or we can use
H缓存或内存中，或者我们可以使用
MongoDB or JBC or hazel caste or you
MongoDB或JBC或榛树种姓或您
know a number of different options here
在这里知道许多不同的选择
but what Redis is a fine choice for this
但是Redis对此是一个不错的选择
so we're gonna add rid of set of
所以我们要删除一组
sessions and we start the application so
会话，我们启动了应用程序，因此
now if we go to where did we say we're
现在，如果我们去哪里，我们说我们在
gonna go to for such orders in the
会在
browser localhost 8080 for special
浏览器localhost 8080特殊
orders
命令
there we go 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 etc now if I
如果我现在去1 2 3 4 5 6 7等
create a new instance go to the same
创建一个新实例去同一个
endpoint you can see it's got this you
端点，你可以看到它已经得到了你
know it's just ID is number 9 so it's
知道这是ID，所以编号是9
obviously a different instance but it's
显然是一个不同的实例，但这是
increasing you know independent each
增加你知道彼此独立
other so right so I've I've got two
其他的对，所以我有两个
different sessions here and that state
这里的不同会议
is being stored in Redis so keys and you
被存储在Redis中，所以密钥和你
can see it says spring sessions expires
可以看到春季课程到期了
and there's another attribute in here
这里还有另一个属性
somewhere if I can there too spring
如果我能在那里也有春天
session expirations spring session etc
会话到期春季会话等
so we've got different sessions being
所以我们有不同的会议
persisted here and managed for us by our
坚持在这里，由我们为我们管理
different application instances so if I
不同的应用程序实例，所以如果我
were to spin up another instance of this
打算把另一个例子
application in this and then and then
在此应用程序然后
somehow
不知何故
call that an application on port 8081
在端口8081上调用该应用程序
for example then given the same cookie
例如然后给相同的cookie
the same clan said cookie I should get
同一氏族说我应该得到饼干
the same result right so there's no
相同的结果，所以没有
that's the you know that's a very simple
那是你知道的，这是非常简单的
example of using Redis as a session it's
使用Redis作为会话的示例
just pluggable where we could actually
只需在我们实际上可以插入的地方
inject the I'm using spring MVC here but
注入我在这里使用spring MVC，但是
you could inject in your spring MVC
您可以注入您的春季MVC
controller you could say HTTP session
控制器，您可以说HTTP会话
session and then do that as well it'll
会议，然后也这样做
work right it'll be in a plug-in to the
工作正常，它将插入
spring session adapter that we've we've
我们拥有的春季会议适配器
automatically configured for you so that
自动为您配置，以便
that works you know independent of the
您知道的独立于
programming model here any you can
您可以在这里编程模型
actually create a web service I had web
实际创建我拥有网络的网络服务
server annotated component you know a
您知道的服务器注释组件
straight-up servlet and then that would
简单的servlet，然后
in turn also don't get to read us here
反过来也不要在这里读我们
so that works at every tier and it just
所以它适用于每个层次
happens for free so now we've got a
免费发生，所以现在我们有一个
horizontally scalable session
水平可扩展会话
persistence which means that if a node
持久性意味着如果一个节点
falls down and they get full they get
跌倒，他们吃饱了，他们得到
load bounds to another node the session
将绑定加载到会话的另一个节点
state hasn't been lost right okay so now
状态还没有丢失好吧，所以现在
now that we've got a web application
现在我们有了一个Web应用程序
we've got a number of different use
我们有许多不同的用途
cases demonstrated here I think we
我想我们在这里展示的案例
should we should deploy this all right
我们应该好好部署吗
so I'm going to take this application
所以我要接受这个申请
I'm gonna add a Cloud Foundry manifest
我要添加一个Cloud Foundry清单
to the application
到应用程序
so CD Redis copy desktop Redis manifest
所以CD Redis复制桌面Redis清单
here and you can see that if I look at
在这里，你可以看到，如果我看着
the manifest the manifest says that the
清单上的清单上说
application is gonna be called spring
应用程序将被称为春季
tips Redis and it's gonna use a banking
提示Redis，它将使用银行业务
service of type spring tip furnace and
弹簧式尖头炉的服务以及
again I'm using pivotal web services
我再次使用关键的Web服务
here and I can go to CF marketplace and
在这里，我可以去CF市场，
I'm being given all the different
我得到了所有不同的
services or service offerings for this
服务或为此提供的服务
hosted multi-tenant cloud offering kind
托管多租户云产品
of like Heroku or something like that
像Heroku或类似的东西
and we have here a Redis instance where
我们这里有一个Redis实例
is our Redis support new relic no PMS
是我们的Redis支持的新产品，没有PMS
equal PQ - cloud Ebola so there's are
等于PQ-云埃博拉病毒，所以有
you know different different quotas
你知道不同的配额
different SLA options here and I've got
这里有不同的SLA选项，我有
a instance of this CF which is sort of
这个CF的实例
for service I've got an instance of this
为了服务，我有一个实例
st vitus Rinna's cloud 100 megabyte plan
st vitus Rinna的云100兆字节计划
and I've got an application called st
我有一个名为st的应用程序
witness i'm gonna now cfd - f st Redis
见证我现在要去cfd-f st Redis
okay so I'm deleting the application
好的，所以我要删除该应用程序
that's already been deployed so it's now
已经被部署，所以现在
being unbound from the Redis instance
与Redis实例解除绑定
and I'm gonna delete the service I'm
我将删除我的服务
gonna delete CFDA - des - f st Redis so
要删除CFDA-des-f st Redis so
I'm deleting the service as well so now
我现在也要删除该服务
we'll have a brand new everything I'm
我们将拥有全新的一切
gonna create the service on new so CF c
会在new上创建服务，因此CF c
s st Redis so we read as cloud 100
s st Redis，所以我们读为云100
megabyte st Redis okay so there we go
兆字节st Redis好，所以我们去了
and now I'm gonna do a maven clean
现在我要做一个行家清洁
package and that's going to build the
包，这将建立
jar the application the Springwood
罐子应用Springwood
application it's gonna run the
应用程序，它将运行
application so we'll see all the same
应用程序，所以我们将看到所有相同的
familiar logging that we saw when we ran
运行时看到的熟悉的日志
the application in the IDE and they're
在IDE中的应用程序
gonna deploy it to the platform alright
要将其部署到平台上
so now we say CF push - P target Venice
所以现在我们说CF push-P target Venice
and we're gonna give it a logical name
我们要给它取一个逻辑名称
called st vitus but we could you know I
叫圣维特，但我们知道吗
think it'll automatically but I think
认为会自动，但我认为
it'll merge this push command with the
它将这个push命令与
manifest but let's just yeah I think I'd
表现出来，但让我想，我想
be fine let's just try it creating app
很好，让我们尝试创建应用
st vitus using round binding this route
st vitus使用圆形绑定此路线
to that uploading this I'm I'm not sure
到上传这个我不确定
if we've already bound the st vitus to
如果我们已经将圣维特绑定到
it or if it's going to consult the
它或如果要咨询
manifest oh yes it is look at that using
体现哦，是的，这是使用
manifest so it is already bound the
清单，因此它已经绑定了
service of the names st vitus to the
圣维特斯名称服务
application so now it's uploading the
应用程序，因此现在它正在上传
application it's gonna the platform is
应用程序，平台将是
gonna look at the incoming artifact it's
看一下传入的工件
gonna realize that it's a jar
会意识到这是一个罐子
application it's gonna give it give it a
应用它会给它一个
file system that has everything needed
具有一切所需的文件系统
to read to run the application in this
阅读以在此运行应用程序
case a job a virtual machine that'll
案例工作的虚拟机将
give it a route which we saw here is st
给它一个我们在这里看到的路线
vitus dot c of apps that i hope and
我希望的应用程序的vitus dot c
let's see what we have here
让我们看看这里有什么
so it's gonna use a build pack that's
所以它将使用一个构建包
the thing that decides what file system
决定什么文件系统的东西
is required to run the application it's
需要运行它的应用程序
gonna choose inevitably the the Java
必然会选择Java
build pack and then it'll start the
构建包，然后它将开始
application up it'll turn that
应用程序将使
filesystem into a container that it'll
文件系统放入一个容器中
then schedule across the cluster now
然后立即在整个群集中计划
what we can do is we can actually
我们能做的是
cluster our application we can say CF
集群我们的应用程序，我们可以说CF
scale - I - and effectively double the
规模-我-实际上是
number of instances of the application
应用程序实例数
itself but they're both talking to the
本身，但他们都在与
same persistent right a store so even if
同样持久的权利商店，即使
we hit different instance of the
我们打了不同的实例
application we'll still get our data
应用程序，我们仍然会获取数据
okay so let's see waiting for the root
好吧，让我们看看等待根
the build packs to kick in
构建包开始
good creating the container uploading
很好创建容器上传
the application
应用程序
now the UM the artifact should hopefully
现在该工件应该是UM
spin up here any moment now upload
现在随时在这里旋转，现在上传
complete
完成
I'll put in complete not sure exactly
我将输入完全不确定
what that is zero of one instance is
一个实例的零是
running one starting
一跑
there we go so there's our application
我们去了所以有我们的应用程序
up and running at this endpoint let's
在此端点启动并运行
try it out okay and it's called orders
好吧，这叫做命令
right so first call second call third
对，所以第一次打电话第二次打电话第三次
call and do the same thing here alright
在这里打电话并做同样的事情
so now we've got an application you know
所以现在我们有了一个您知道的应用程序
two different two different sessions
两个不同的两个不同的会议
being persisted now let's actually go
被坚持现在让我们去
ahead and scale this up okay so CF scale
向前并扩大规模，这样CF规模
- I - st - right so I'm going to double
-我-圣-对，所以我要加倍
the load on that application instance CF
该应用程序实例CF上的负载
logs I'm gonna follow the logs now for
我现在要关注的日志
this instance so as I make requests over
这个实例，当我提出请求
here you can see they request coming
在这里你可以看到他们要求来
into the application on the left so
进入左侧的应用程序
router 11 router of 0 let's see where
路由器11的路由器0，让我们看看
does it actually indicate yeah also the
它实际上表明是吗
other application is still coming up app
其他应用程序仍在运行中
proc web 1 good so we got now two
proc web 1好，所以我们现在得到了两个
different apps being configured a way
配置不同应用程序的方式
for them to spin up and we'll start to
让他们旋转起来，我们将开始
be able to round-robin the requests
能够轮询请求
across multiple instances all right so
跨多个实例好吧
okay refresh refresh refresh notice how
好的，刷新，刷新，刷新，注意如何
in this case since we're running its we
在这种情况下，因为我们正在运行它
have the same session but it was handled
有相同的会话，但已处理
on a different JVM and we know that it's
在不同的JVM上，我们知道
been handled on a JVM because the ID is
已在JVM上处理，因为ID为
3 all right so remember we have that
3好吧，记住我们有
private atomic long well this is JVM
长期以来，这是JVM
specific you know its intrinsic state
具体你知道它的内在状态
but the internal state the external
但是内部状态是外部
state which is the session itself that's
状态是会话本身
being managed by Redis all that's just
由Redis管理，仅此而已
transparent so you know and we have the
透明的，所以你知道，我们有
same host and we have the same it should
同一主机，我们应该具有相同的主机
be cookie same session cookie it's
是cookie同一会话cookie
hitting the same host you know we have a
击中同一台主机，您知道我们有一个
load bouncer behind the scenes and we're
在后台加载保镖，我们
getting different sessions right we're
正确地进行不同的会话
getting different application instances
获得不同的应用程序实例
we know that because the application of
我们知道，因为
state is different across those
那些州的情况不同
different ATMs and but we are still able
不同的ATM，但我们仍然能够
to see and work with the same shopping
看到和一起购物
cart on both notes so this is one of the
两个便笺上的购物车，所以这是其中之一
examples of Redis just being a
Redis的例子只是
transparent you know thing that you can
透明，你知道你可以做的事情
just layer down into layer into your
只是分层到您的
application and get all this amazing
应用程序，并获得所有这些惊人的
functionality
功能性
now we've long we've looked at a few
现在我们已经很长时间了
different things here we looked at
我们在这里看到了不同的东西
caching related meditation sheepy
缓存相关的冥想
sessions we looked at repositories we
会议，我们看了仓库
looked at geography geospatial support I
看了地理地理空间支持我
would have to publish/subscribe support
将不得不发布/订阅支持
we looked at you know you know caching
我们看着你知道你知道缓存
just generic caching itself we looked at
只是通用缓存本身
a number of different things here but
这里有很多不同的东西，但是
we've only begun to scratch the surface
我们才刚刚开始刮擦表面
Redis is as I say a variable Swiss Army
正如我所说，Redis是一支多变的瑞士军队
knife of functionality it supports on a
它支持的功能刀
number of different things and in the
不同事物的数量和
spring ecosystem we use it to great
春天的生态系统，我们可以很好地利用它
effect and every layer that we can so we
效果以及我们可以做到的每一层
even have a project called spring pod
甚至有一个名为spring pod的项目
gateway it is built on top of the
网关建立在
reactive support in you know in Spring
您在春季知道的反应式支持
Framework five spring web flux and all
框架五，弹簧网通量及全部
that and I've done previous videos on
那，我已经完成了以前的视频
spring card gateway itself and there we
弹簧卡网关本身，在那里我们
looked at using spring cloud game we
看着使用春季云游戏我们
need to create a rate limiter well it
需要很好地创建一个速率限制器
has to keep external state extrinsic
必须保持外部状态外在
state somewhere so it creates tours that
声明某个地方，以便创建游览
in Redis for example and that's actually
例如在Redis中，实际上
using their reactive Redis spring data
使用他们的反应性Redis弹簧数据
module which I haven't even bothered to
我什至没有去过的模块
use here because it's it's still just
在这里使用，因为它仍然只是
you know all these ideas apply it's just
你知道所有这些想法都适用
very convenient to know that you can use
知道可以使用非常方便
this in a traditional
这是传统的
servlet based architecture as well so
基于servlet的架构
with that my friends thank you so much
我的朋友非常感谢你
for watching I hope you enjoyed we'll
看我希望你喜欢我们
see
看到
next time
下次
you
您